Let's take a trading position, so
I feel we should buy ICICI Lombard
from here, it is trading
around 1974-76, from June 4 till today, the
stock has bridged its high only once in 20 days
and that too it
reclaimed it on the same day and in a rising trend,
you can see a good structure on all the charts, daily, weekly and monthly,
and
I feel there will be
a pullback in insurance stocks here, and
especially on ICICI Lombard,
my opinion will be to buy ICICI Lombard from the current price, with a
stop loss of 1940 and two
targets of 2020 and 2040 within the next three to four sessions, okay, let's take
a fundamental call now,
Gorang Shah has joined us, let's
talk to him, Gorang ji, good
afternoon, which stock came in your radar,
thank you, Anu ji, greetings to everyone and a
good day, Happy Independence Day from our side,
CNBC Awas viewers to you, the
entire CNBC Awas team and everyone on the platform  To
all the dignitaries present here,
in the financial sector we have selected Mahendra &
Mahendra Finance and Enam Finance
and after seeing the results